Guide to the C-SPAN records, 1809, 1978-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 7: Education and Marketing (Boxes 145-229), 1989-2009
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Alberto Fujimori, September 18, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Lynn Martin, September 19, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Robert Dallek, September 22, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Program Transcript-Lynne Cheney, September 24-25, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Stephen Carter, September 29, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Barbara Mikulski, September 30, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 11)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Newton Minow, October 2, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 12)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Ken Auletta, October 6, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 13)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Cathleen Black, October 7, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 14)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Igor Golembiovsky, October 10, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 15)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-John Kenneth Galbraith, October 16, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 16)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Anthony Lewis, October 20, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 17)
  - Program Transcript-Economic Policy Institute-"Investing in America's Future"-Multiple Speakers, October 21, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 18)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Vaclav Havel, October 23, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 19)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Phil Donahue and Vladimir Posner, October 24, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 20)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Dan Oberdorfer, October 27, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 21)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Edward Madigan, October 29, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 22)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Lt. Col. Oliver North, October 31, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 23)
  - Program Transcript-Coalition for Better Government-H. Ross Perot, November 2, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 24)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Larry Sabato, November 3, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 25)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Robert Kerrey, November 4, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 26)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Tina Rosenberg, November 10, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 27)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Warren Burger, November 15, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 28)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Suzanne Garment, November 17, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 29)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-James B. Stewart, November 24, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 30)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Gary Sick, December 1, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 31)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Harris Wofford, December 2, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 32)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Carl Lewis, December 6, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 33)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-James Reston, December 8, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 34)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Gore Vidal, December 10, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 35)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Jay Leno, December 12, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 36)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Robert Strauss, December 13, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 37)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Thomas Edsall, December 15, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 38)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Martin Gilbert, December 22, 1991 (Box 224, Folder 39)
  - Program Transcript-Map Room of White House with George Bush, December 22, 1991 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-James Breslin, December 29, 1991 (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-J. Carter Brown, January 7, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Program Transcript-Economic Club of Detroit-Lee Iacocca, January 10, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 4)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Oliver Stone, January 15, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 5)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-George Mitchell, January 16, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 6)
  - Program Transcript-"JFK: Cinema as History" Speakers, January 22, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 7)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Thomas Foley, January 23, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 8)
  - Program Transcript-An American Profile-Louis Rukeyser, January 27, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 9)
  - Program Transcript-The State of the Union Address-President George Bush, January 28, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 10)
  - Program Transcript-State of the Union Democratic Response by Thomas Foley, January 28, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 11)
  - Program Transcript-Democratic Issues Conference-Various Speakers, January 30, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 12)
  - Program Transcript-Orange County Forum-Milton Friedman, February 11, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 13)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Harrison Salisbury, February 26, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 14)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Richard Nixon, February 23, March 1, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 15)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Lloyd Bentsen, March 4, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 16)
  - Program Transcript-Nixon Library Conference-Henry Kissinger, March 12, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 17)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Dan Rather, March 16, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 18)
  - Program Transcript-An American Profile-H. Ross Perot, March 18, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 19)
  - Program Transcript-Freedom Forum-Salman Rushdie, March 24, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 20)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-David Belin, March 26, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 21)
  - Program Transcript-Road to the White House-H. Ross Perot, Pat Buchanan, Allan Lichtman, April 8, 10, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 22)
  - Program Transcript-Viewer Call-In-H. Ross Perot, April 10, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 23)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Marian Wright Edelman, April 14, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 24)
  - Program Transcript-An American Profile-James Rouse, April 17, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 25)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-T. Berry Brazelton, April 24, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 26)
  - Program Transcript-Anita Hill-Conference on Parity, Power and Sexual Harassment, April 25, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 27)
  - Program Transcript-H. Ross Perot-American Newspaper Publishers Association, May 5, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 28)
  - Program Transcript-Road to the White House-H. Ross Perot, May 17, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 29)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Robert Bartley, May 17, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 30)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Arthur Ashe, May 26, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 31)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Lester Thurow, May 28, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 32)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Lester Thurow, May 31, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 33)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Daniel Patrick Moynihan, June 5, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 34)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-R. Emmett Tyrell, June 7, 1992 (Box 225, Folder 35)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Patricia Ireland, June 12, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Sir Edmund Hillary, June 26, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-David Savage, June 28, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Chief Justice William Rehnquist, July 7, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-David McCullough, July 19, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 5)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Richard Ben Cramer, July 26, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - Program Transcript-J. Peter Grace-Speech to the International Platform Association, August 4, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Martin Anderson, August 16, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 8)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Neil Postman, August 30, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 9)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Christopher Whittle and Benno Schmidt, September 17, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 10)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Senator Paul Simon, September 20, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 11)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Ron Carey, September 23, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 12)
  - Program Transcript-First Presidential Debate-Bush, Clinton, Perot, October 11, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 13)
  - Program Transcript-Third Presidential Debate-Bush, Clinton, Perot, October 19, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 14)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Warren Rudman and Paul Tsongas, October 20, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 15)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Susan Faludi, October 25, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 16)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Dr. Jack Kevorkian, October 27, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 17)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Dave Barry, November 12, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 18)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Gen. Norman Schwarzkopf, November 22, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 19)
  - Program Transcript-Jimmy Carter-Speech to the Town Hall of California, November 24, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 20)
  - Program Transcript-Tip O'Neill, November 26, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 21)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Charles Sykes, November 29, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 22)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Neil Rudenstine, November 30, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 23)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Daniel Boorstin, December 6, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 24)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Brian Kelly, December 13, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 25)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Michael Medved, December 28, 1992 (Box 226, Folder 26)
  - Program Transcript-An American Profile-R.W. Apple, January 1, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 27)
  - Program Transcript-An American Profile-Jim Lehrer, January 1, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 28)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Jeffrey Birnbaum, January 10, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 29)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-James Carville, January 19 1993 (Box 226, Folder 30)
  - Program Transcript-Presidential Inauguration-President Bill Clinton, January 20, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 31)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Robert E. Gilbert, January 24, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 32)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Roy Romer, January 29, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 33)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Benjamin J. Stein, January 31, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 34)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Jack Nelson, February 7, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 35)
  - Program Transcript-Economic Address to Congress-President Bill Clinton, February 17, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 36)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Lloyd Bentsen-Secretary, Department of the Treasury, February 19, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Peter Arnett, February 20, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Richard Norton Smith, February 21, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Harold "Red" Poling, February 23, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 4)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-James Courter, March 5, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 5)
  - Program Transcript-An American Profile-Thomas "Mack" McLarty, March 7, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 6)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Paul Kennedy, March 14, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 7)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Terry Anderson, March 16, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-H. Ross Perot, March 18, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Nadine Cohodas, April 4, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 10)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Coretta Scott King, April 8, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 11)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Blanche Wiesen Cook, April 11, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - Program Transcript-Federal Office Systems Exposition-Bill Gates, April 13, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 13)
  - Program Transcript-"The Role of Men and Women in the '90s"-Phyllis Schlafly, April 15, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 14)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-The Dalai Lama, April 29, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 15)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Robert Dole, April 30, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 16)
  - Program Transcript-Janet Reno-Speech Before the Rainbow Coalition, June 10, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 17)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-David Brock, June 13, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 18)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Janet Reno, July 1, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 19)
  - Program Transcript-Conversation-Sen. Howard Baker, Jeane Kirkpatrick, Pierre Salinger, July 5, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 20)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-David Halberstam, July 11, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 21)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-David Remnick, July 25, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 22)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Peter Collier, August 7, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 23)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Lewis Lapham, August 15, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 24)
  - Program Transcript-Conversation-H. Ross Perot, August 19, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 25)
  - Program Transcript-Center for National Policy-Robert Reich, September 1, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 26)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Ronald Kessler, September 12, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 27)
  - Program Transcript-Conversation-Walter Cronkite, September 12, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 28)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Madeline Cartwright, September 19, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 29)
  - Program Transcript-President Bill Clinton-Health Care Address to Congress, September 22, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 30)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Christopher Hitchens, October 17, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 31)
  - Program Transcript-Business for Social Responsibility Conference-Lester Thurow, October 21, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Margaret Thatcher, November 5, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Charles L. Mee, Jr., November 7, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Bobby Knight, November 11, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - Program Transcript-International Radio and Television Society-Mario Cuomo, November 30, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Margaret Thatcher, December 5, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Norman Lear, December 9, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Richard Reeves, December 12, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 8)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-John Podhoretz, December 19, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 9)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Vice President Al Gore, December 21, 1993 (Box 228, Folder 10)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-William Bennett, January 9, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 11)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Carolyn Barta, January 16, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 12)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Gary Hymel, January 23, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 13)
  - Program Transcript-President Bill Clinton-State of the Union Address, January 25, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 14)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-William H. Chafe, January 30, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 15)
  - Program Transcript-Stanley Weintraub, February 6, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 16)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Bill Emmott, February 13, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 17)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Steven Lesher, February 27, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 18)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Norman Ornstein, March 13, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 19)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Clare Brandt, March 20, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 20)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Andrew Young, April 3, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 21)
  - Program Transcript-Radio and Television Correspondents Association-President Bill Clinton, Garrison Keillor, April 12, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 22)
  - Program Transcript-Business for Social Responsibility Conference-Ben Cohen, April 21, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 23)
  - Program Transcript-Lady Margaret Thatcher, April 25, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 24)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Forrest McDonald, May 15, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 25)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-James M. McPherson, May 22, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 26)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Joseph Cardinal Bernardin, May 26, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 27)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Pete Hamill, May 29, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 28)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Stephen Ambrose, June 5, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 29)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Mark Neely, Jr., June 12, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 30)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Lani Guinier, June 26, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 31)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Murray Kempton, July 3, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 32)
  - Program Transcript-Accuracy in Academia Conference-David Horowitz, July 8, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 33)
  - Program Transcript-Accuracy in Academia Conference, Washington D.C.-David Thibodaux, July 9, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 34)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Cal Thomas, July 10, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 35)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-David Hackett Fischer, July 17, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 36)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Dan Quayle, July 24, 1994 (Box 228, Folder 37)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Colman McCarthy, July 31, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Merrill Peterson, August 14, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Hugh Pearson, August 21, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-John Leo, 34574 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Paul H. Weaver, September 4, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - Program Transcript-United We Stand America-H. Ross Perot, September 9, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Shelby Foote, September 11, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Ken Burns, September 12, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Irving H. Bartlett, September 18, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 9)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Ben Yagoda, September 25, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 10)
  - Program Transcript-National Press Club-Barbara Jordan, September 30, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 11)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Nicholas Kristof and Sheryl WuDunn, October 16, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 12)
  - Program Transcript-Booknotes-Bill Thomas, November 6, 1994 (Box 229, Folder 13)
- Series 8: Executive Files and Correspondence (Boxes 229-402), 1976-2009
  Executive Files and Correspondence (1976-2009) includes the majority of Lamb's personal correspondence with a number of individuals and organizations. Also includes documents related to C-SPAN's operating budget, Board Meetings and Executive Committee Meetings memoranda, press clippings, "Booknotes" materials and manuscripts, tour speeches, C-SPAN 2000, 20th Anniversary planning materials, and court documents.
  - Board Meeting, September 21, 1978 (Box 229, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers and Newsletters, 1978 (Box 229, Folder 15)
  - National Press Club History, 1982-1984 (Box 229, Folder 16)
  - Excerpt From Man of the House Tip O'Neill, 1987 (Box 229, Folder 17)
  - Cablevision Brian Lamb Interviews Richard Wiley, October 25, 1976 (Box 229, Folder 18)
  - History of C-SPAN, 1978 (Box 229, Folder 19)
  - Professional Correspondence Outgoing, 1979 (Box 229, Folder 20)
  - Professional Correspondence Incoming, 1979 (Box 229, Folder 21)
  - Cost-Sharing Agreement, March 1, 1979 (Box 229, Folder 22)
  - [Wendall?] Ford Excerpts on Televising, U.S. Senate, April 15,[1984?] (Box 229, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors General Correspondence, 1978-1987 (Box 229, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors Weekly Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 229, Folder 25)
  - Launch Kit, 1978 (Box 229, Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, November 6, 1978-July 20, 1979 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Affiliate Coverage Rejection Letters, 1979-1982 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - Cablevision Articles, May-October 1978 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Members and Meeting Locations, 1978-1987 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - Close Up Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - Professional Correspondence Outgoing, 1978 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - Charles D. Ferris Speeches at National Cable Television Association, 1978-1979 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - Charlie Rose Speech at the Western Cable Television Show, December 1978 (Box 230, Folder 8)
  - Preparations to Broadcast U.S. House of Representatives, 1978 (Box 230, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Memos, and Notes, 1981-1984 (Box 230, Folder 10)
  - Cablevision, 1976-1979 (Box 230, Folder 11)
  - Coverage of C-SPAN Launch, 1979 (Box 230, Folder 12)
  - Affiliate Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - Coverage of C-SPAN Launch, 1979-1980 (Box 230, Folder 14)
  - Wall St. Journal Article on C-SPAN Launch, March 26, 1979 (Box 230, Folder 15)
  - Washington Post Coverage of C-SPAN Launch, 1979 (Box 230, Folder 16)
  - TV Guide Coverage of C-SPAN Launch, 1979 (Box 230, Folder 17)
  - Washington Star Coverage of C-SPAN Launch, 1979 (Box 230, Folder 18)
  - Cable Industry Newsletter Coverage and Correspondence on the C-SPAN Launch, 1979 (Box 230, Folder 19)
  - Magazine Coverage of C-SPAN Launch, 1979 (Box 230, Folder 20)
  - Various Newspaper Coverage of C-SPAN Launch, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles Times Coverage of C-SPAN Launch, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - New York Times Coverage of C-SPAN Launch, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Record Mentions of C-SPAN, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Record, April 3, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Record, June 15, September 17, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Record, 1977, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - News Releases, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 8)
  - National Press Club Correspondence, 1979 (Box 231, Folder 9)
  - University Research Project "TV Coverage of the House,", 1979 (Box 231, Folder 10)
  - Interoffice Communication, 1981 (Box 231, Folder 11)
  - Professional Correspondence Outgoing, 1981 (Box 231, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, August-December 1985 (Box 231, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 231, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence, April-October 1985 (Box 231, Folder 15)
  - Board Correspondence, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Weekly Reports, January-October 1985 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Paul Fitzpatrick Incoming Correspondence, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Bruce Collins Outgoing Correspondence, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence Outgoing, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - Mike Michaelson Outgoing Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Paul Fitzpatrick Outgoing Correspondence, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - Brian Lamb Outgoing Correspondence, 1985 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 232, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, January-June 1984 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Internal Correspondence and Memorandum, 1984 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - Internal Correspondence and Memoranda, 1984 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - Board Correspondence, 1984 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Board Correspondence, 1984 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Letter to Educational Publications on C-SPAN in the Classroom, September 24, 1986 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations Correspondence, November 1986 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - Tax Reform Hearings Coverage Request Letters, July 9, 1986 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Outgoing, 1984 (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - Bruce Collins Correspondence, 1982 (Box 233, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 233, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 233, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, July-December 1984 (Box 233, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Outgoing, 1983 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, January-March 1985 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - Board Correspondence, 1983 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - Internal Correspondence and Memoranda, 1983 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - Brian Lamb Appointment Book, 1984 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - Brian Lamb Appointment Book, 1985 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - Brian Lamb Appointment Books, 1985 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 234, Folder 9)
  - Update Subscription Report, April-June 1987 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - Constitution Bicentennial Commission, 1986 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - Studies About C-SPAN, January-May 1985 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - Studies On Media And Advertising, 1985 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Reaching The Top: U.S.-Soviet Summitry Since 1955, 1985 (Box 235, Folder 5)